<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diana Tran</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Diana Tran</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafts!!</title>
      <link>/blog/crafts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/crafts/</guid>
      <description>Crafts from over the years Here are some of the things I’ve made from the past couple of years that I’m probably the most proud of :-)
 Paintings/calligraphy a painting for a service event (2017) A painting for a mentor (1 of 2) (2016) A painting for a mentor (2 of 2) (2016) A holiday card made for a friend (2016)
 Embroidery A thank you gift for a friend headed to Texas State (2016)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python</title>
      <link>/blog/python-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/python-stuff/</guid>
      <description>Python discussion This is the blog post that is dedicated to Python and what we’ve learned in class. The thing I most enjoyed about Python this semester was what we learned for homework 11 where our task was to use regular expressions in python to match (and return) the requested parts in each. I just really enjoyed the process of looking for patterns in the strings that could ultimately be used in the re.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects: Here are the two projects from this semester:
Project 1 (Data Wrangling and Exploratory Analysis)
 Project 1  Project 2 (Modeling, Inference, Prediction)
 Project 2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The first dataset included in this project includes gender gap information by nation- the countries were ranked/scored via reports from the World Economic Forum (links to each were included as a column in the dataset). The rankings were out of 142 countries from information that was collected in 2014, and the overall scores are based ona scale from 0.0 to 1.00, 0.0 = inequality up to 1.00 = equality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, Predicting</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>library(tidyverse) library(tidyr)  Introduction The dataset I chose for this project is comprised of the nutrition data on 77 different cereal products. It includes the name of the cereal, the manufactuerer of the cereal (A= American Home Good Products, G= General Mills, K = Kelloggs, N= Nabisco, P = Post, Q = Quaker Oats, R = Ralston purina), the type (C= cold, H = hot), the calories (per serving), the grams of protein,milligrams of sodium, grams of dietary fiber, grams of complex carbohydrates, the grams of sugar, milligrams of potassium, vitamins (percentage of FDA recommended), display shelf, wieght in ounces in one serving, cups in one serving, and lastly the rating of the cereal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>